Previously on Raising Kanan...
Fiends come in.
ask for the special.
Richard and Sunny here
serve that shit up.
- This gon' be your spot.
- Fuck you.
Call a damn plumber.
Calling the plumber's
the landlord's job.
What the fuck do I know
about being a damn landlord?
It ain't me.
Are you pregnant? Have
you ever been pregnant?
Do you plan on
becoming pregnant?
- No.
- You don't want to show up
to basic training with
a baby in your belly.
That's not gonna happen.
I know how that gun
got in your bag. K.
It was your moms.
You didn't do shit?
You got five minutes
to pack your shit
and get the fuck
outta here. man.
But what about all the shit
you did to cover it up. Malcolm?
You had Sam killed.
I know it was you.
And if you did
that. who knows...
I don't know why
Burke killed herself.
But it's in everyone's
best interest.
especially Burke's family.
that we close the file on
this as soon as possible.
Captain Burke. I'm Adina Foyle.
There's something
you need to know.
Whatever it was that
you two were doing
is a big part of why
Shannon did what she did.
So I've been talkin' to
Ogden. over in Narcotics?
Turns out. he's gonna
hang 'em up soon.
And you want his job.
Let me make some calls.
- Thanks. Cap.
- I'm the big dog. nigga.
Takin' out Deen
and runnin' your fuckin'
mouth to Pernessa
ain't no big-dog shit.
That's bitch shit.
You know. I heard about
our friend Unique.
I'm sorry.
I wanna step into what
he started with you.
- take it over.
- Let's give it
the old college try.
Now that you're back in.
there's only one way out.
The name of the group is Butta.
If they like what they see.
we'll be in a studio
within two weeks.
If they don't like you.
Butta is just another baby
that never should've been born.
- Yo.
- Cut the music.
Iesha. this my cousin.
- Kanan.
- Iesha.
Don't be a dick to this girl.
And we in this group together.
Hey. you are fuckin'
up my business. Kanan.
What if I told the cops about
what you're doin' here. huh?
Bet that'd change things
pretty fuckin' fast.
You on that nickel and
dime shit right now.
But together we can
make real money.
Snaps and me. we don't
deal with the day-to-day.
We just put some money up.
- You want heroin.
- We talkin' 'bout
different work. shit that's got
a higher upside
and's easier to move.
I miss our group. Marvin.
We could have our
own shit. you know?
Keep each other
correct and shit.
How old your daughters again?
Five and seven.
A story about your daughter
might make a lot
of sense for me.
My boy didn't kill himself.
Someone put a bullet
in my son's head.
Scrap didn't deserve
how we did him. man.
It's my fault. you know?
It's my fault that...
That your son's dead.
He not here no more.
and it's my fault.
I'm so fuckin' sorry.
♪ I'm a hustler. baby
I'm a hustler. baby ♪
♪ Yeah. I know
Heartbreaks. setbacks ♪
♪ Bitch. if I crap out
I'm sure I'ma get back ♪
♪ I been through the ups and
Downs. you know I get around ♪
♪ So to me It's all
a part of the game ♪
♪ If I ain't the coke
man Or the dope man ♪
♪ I'm almost for sure.
man I got to take it ♪
♪ No need to say shit
I'm gon' take it ♪
♪ Robberies turned homicide
It's nothin' to play with ♪
♪ Make money Make.
make. make money ♪
♪ When shit hit the fan
We'll take money. Southside ♪
♪ Beef with the best of 'em ♪
♪ Done shot At the
rest of 'em. yeah ♪
♪ Checks. I'm collectin' 'em ♪
♪ Check. boy I'm
finessin' 'em ♪
♪ Bag Supreme Boy.
you fuck around ♪
♪ Put a big bag on your head ♪
♪ Before the weather
break You're dead ♪
♪ Let's get to it. they
Don't do it like we do it ♪
♪ Nah. cop it. whip
it Bag it. flip it ♪
♪ Re-up. we up
G'd up. what up? ♪
♪ Runnin' round this bitch
Still not givin' a fuck. hey ♪
♪ When it come to that paper
There'll be no complications ♪
Ha ha. That's right.
♪ Put a hole in a nigga
Right in front of you ♪
♪ Your heartbeat pacin' ♪
♪ And it's all right ♪
♪ That's how We do
it on this side ♪
♪ Niggas get to
it On this side ♪
♪ I know heartbreaks
Setbacks ♪
♪ Bitch. if I crap out
I'm sure I'ma get back ♪
♪ I been through the ups and
Downs. you know I get around ♪
♪ So to me It's all
a part of the game ♪
♪ If I ain't the coke
man Or the dope man ♪
♪ I'm almost for sure.
man I got to take it ♪
♪ No need to say shit
I'm gon' take it ♪
♪ Robberies turned homicide
It's nothin' to play with ♪
♪ Hey. hey ♪
- ♪ Tennessee ♪
- ♪ Lord. I've ♪
♪ Really been real stressed ♪
♪ Down and out... ♪
Eight-letter word for loose.
Ends with the letter S.
Your moms.
No.
♪ Where I can go To
let these ghosts... ♪
Careless. Careless.
♪ My grandma's passed ♪
♪ My brother's gone ♪
♪ I never ever at
once Felt so alone ♪
♪ I know you're supposed
to be My steering wheel ♪
♪ Not just my spare tire... ♪
Yo. what the fuck?
Yo. yo. yo. yo.
What is this. man?
Who the fuck are you?
A lot of fools think
they can do this work.
Think this hustle just
like anything else.
You want money? Just
tell me what you want.
I can take care...
But this ain't business
as usual. nigga.
♪
Forget All that hurts me... ♪
And it ain't for everybody.
♪
Understand your plans ♪
- ♪ Take me to another place ♪
- ♪ Home ♪
- ♪ Take me to another land ♪
♪ Make me forget
All that hurts me ♪
♪ Let me understand
Your plan ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Tennessee ♪
- ♪ Tennessee. whoo. yeah ♪
♪ Tennessee ♪
Word. I got you.
Man. Primo round the
corner right now.
Fuck! Shit. Yo!
I gotta go.
Yo. Yo. Kanan.
J-Just... you gotta tell
them that I'm cool. okay?
They-they-they don't need to
hurt me anymore. all right?
But you not cool. though. Paul.
That's Ronnie. my new partner.
Ronnie don't like that
shit you was talkin'
'bout goin' to the police.
Don't like that shit at all.
The fuck you doin' here?
M-my bad. I c-I can just
come back another time.
Where you goin'?
Um. y'all look busy.
So I was just gon' leave.
You ain't gotta leave.
Look. I'm sorry. man.
I-I-I was never gonna
call the police. man.
I-I was just sayin' it
'cause I was frustrated.
Sayin' it worse than doin' it.
I won't-I won't
say it. then. man.
I promise. I won't-I
won't even think it.
Get up.
You pissed yourself.
We gotta get you cleaned up.
Give you all some privacy.
Nah. I'm right behind you.
I just came to get
the rest of my shit
'cause I-I couldn't
get it before.
I gotta go make sure Ronnie
don't kill this nigga.
Just get your shit and be
gone before I get back.
Nothin' changes on your end.
Same numbers. same setup.
You just fuckin' with me
now instead of 'Nique.
Thank you.
I think I'll pass.
The one location
Unique was runnin'
was already more trouble
than it was worth.
He had talked about expanding.
but he couldn't get
the pieces in place.
especially transportation.
Moving this product
around the city undetected
isn't as easy as it seems.
Now that Unique is dead.
that deal is too.
I appreciate your interest.
I can build this business.
I've done it before.
I'll do it again.
I wouldn't be here to
run work outta one shop.
That's not worth my time.
I got big ideas. larger plans.
The fishmonger
told me who you are
and what you've done.
But you need to
understand that this
is a different business
than the one you were in.
I'm not some beaner
importing product
in the bellies of young girls.
This is a sophisticated
operation here.
It's a different ball game.
You got the ball.
I got the players.
You aren't the only team.
But my team wins.
Okay. Why not?
What do I really have to lose?
I'll give you two months
to build your operation
into something that
generates real money.
If you don't get
there. we're done.
No consignment. no excuses.
You pay on delivery.
You get me the work.
I'll get you paid.
What's in the bag?
It's my shit.
I'm-I'm movin' back to my moms'.
What's wrong with livin' here?
Nothin' at all.
Um. she just-she just
misses me. that's it.
What she miss about you?
What?
The fuck so good about you
that your moms miss you?
I mean. I'm her... son?
I'm my moms' son.
She don't miss me.
I don't know why my
mom misses me. then.
I guess you just gon'
have to ask her that.
Maybe she miss your voice.
Kanan says you talk... a lot.
You for real? You
said that shit?
- Look. I...
- Nobody likes talkin'...
'cept maybe your moms.
I don't talk.
I don't talk to nobody.
I'm... I-I promise.
You-you don't gotta worry
about that shit at all.
I...
I look worried to you. nigga?
No.
You sayin' I look shook?
That's what you sayin'?
'Cause I can show you
what shook feel like.
I'm not sayin' that.
I'm just-I'm just
sayin' I don't talk
and I-I'm not that
type of person.
I never have. I...
K. could you tell him
that shit. please?
Fame keep shit close. mostly.
If he don't. I'll
fuck him up myself.
I'll hit at y'all later.
So Marvin Thomas.
Ogden over at Queens Narcotics
gave us some
information on this guy
but nothing really
beyond his record.
Does the neighborhood have
a point of view on him?
In what way?
I could give you
a better road map
if I knew where you
guys were headed.
Like I keep telling you.
there's only so much I can say.
We have to keep our work close
because it touches on so many
different investigations
and suspects.
You know I'm up for Ogden's job.
And once you have it.
I will drop my pants
for you. Howard.
Until then.
the information flow between
us is a one-way proposition.
So. back to one Marvin Thomas.
Marvin hungry. Always has been.
Got a reputation around the
way for bein' a tough guy.
Don't take no shit
off of nobody.
I hadn't heard nothin'
about him havin'
Italian connects. but it tracks.
The Mob has hands all
over the drug trade.
So makes sense they
would bump into him.
So you think he's
capable of the operations
at Baisley and the
South Jamaica houses?
It's not outside the
realm of possibility.
You know who you should talk to?
Detective Peng over there.
He knows these streets
as well as anyone.
Let me get him for you.
Looks like he's in the
middle of something.
Nah. that's just this
neighborhood broad
always complainin'
'bout parking tickets.
Give me a second.
I know now for sure.
I heard it from
someone who was there.
Yo. Peng. let me holler
at you right quick.
Excuse me for a second.
Tanner from the task force.
he wants to talk to you.
- Really? Right now?
- Yeah.
Look. I'll handle
her. but you owe me.
Shit.
Thanks. Howard.
Detective Howard here
is gonna hear you out.
He's gonna take notes and
tell me everything you say.
Wait. where are you going?
You need to know what I know!
You can tell me.
I promise I'm a good listener.
But I know Peng.
Now you gonna get to know me.
Tell me what's on your mind.
Let me see if I can help.
I'm here about a murder.
The murder of my son.
I'm all ears.
What the fuck?
Yo. um...
yo. what y'all doin'? Y'all...
You okay?
Our dad told us to wait here.
How long ago?
He said he'd come get us
when it was time to come in.
No. man. you're...
y'all two gonna freeze out here.
Get you two inside.
What the fuck. Gerald?
H-hey. Marvin.
It's good to see you. man.
So to what do I
owe this pleasure?
- And who told you all this?
- I can't say.
You have a witness to
the murder of your son
but you can't tell me who it is?
You know how this
works. Detective.
If people knew I was talkin'...
But it's just me
and you in here.
Mm.
And I assume you want
us to investigate
whatever it is you
think you know.
Lou Thomas. He the
one who told me.
Hold on. hold on. so you sayin'
Lou Thomas was there
when your son got shot?
It sounded like it. yeah.
Uh. what does "it
sounded like it" mean?
He was either
there. or he wasn't.
Look. we gotta get our
ducks in a row here
for you and your son's sake.
This-this is a big deal.
Can't have no mistakes.
no oversights.
Look. Lou was a little
all over the place
when he was talkin' with me.
He might have had a drink
before he came over.
So he was drunk.
Confessions and
statements by drunk folks
don't hold up in court.
He told me my son was murdered.
I'm just sayin'. based on
what you've given me...
a drunk guy tellin'
you that he knows
about the commission
of a crime...
that's not a whole lot.
My boy didn't kill himself.
I'll look into it.
But don't talk to nobody else
- about it.
- Mm.
Not even no other police.
Last thing I want is
you speakin' on this
around the way
and. like you said.
people get it in they
head that you snitchin'.
Because that's when
bad things happen.
What the fuck is this. man?
You in here gettin' high
on this fuckin' shit
and them kids
outside in the cold?
How long was they in the car?
Few minutes. A half hour.
A couple hours at the most.
You gonna hurt somebody.
somebody who ain't you.
- I'm gonna make some lunch.
- You need any help?
I don't. mi amor. but thank you.
I got you.
You okay?
Yeah. I'm. uh... I'm...
Yeah. I'm good.
I was scared. Shawn.
I didn't know what else to do.
That's why I told you to leave.
You were right. though.
I was actin' like a clown and...
I'm not gonna do that again.
And I'm not gonna tell
you to leave again.
I got into a lot
of stupid shit. Ma.
Some shit I wish
I never did and...
I can't undo it.
Don't think about that now.
You're home.
- I love you. Ma.
- I love you too.
They'll be performing
to a prerecorded track.
so we'll need playback.
And send me the stage
specs so I can take a look.
Thank you.
Guess who just got a gig
at the Garden State Mall
openin' up for Shanice?
Congratulations. ladies.
We're movin' in the
right direction.
I want shots of each of
the girls out in front
so I can see how they look.
Make the camera
love you. ladies...
and maybe I will too.
♪ I'm so fed up Time
to get up. baby... ♪
Well. I guess
you're front first.
♪ I thought that what we had ♪
♪ Would never end... ♪
Let's do this.
Nice.
♪ But now it's too late ♪
♪ For my heart to mend... ♪
Keep goin'.
Just like that.
Your stupid-ass little brother
went to Scrap mom's house drunk
and spilled the whole shit.
And then she came
to the precinct.
Lucky for yo' ass. I got
in between that shit.
Is there anything
you don't fuck up?
This ain't on me.
This my brother.
It's your peoples.
It's your fuck-up.
Look. the only
reason you even care
is 'cause the shit
tracks back to you
and your fuck-up on Scrap.
Don't you never forget I can
burn your shit down to
the ground. Detective.
I'll handle Lou.
What about that
task force bullshit?
What they gettin' into?
They ain't got
nothin' on nobody.
No suspects at all.
- Thank you.
Guess what I have.
Found some cookies for dessert.
Y'all can eat 'em upstairs.
Share 'em with your sister.
These ain't all for you.
Thanks. Uncle Marvin.
You did your homework. right?
We don't have any.
What kind of school
doesn't have homework?
Must be in the Bronx.
There's really no amount
of gratitude I can express
that will adequately
articulate my appreciation
for what you've done here.
Look. I don't even know
what the fuck all that means.
But what if I didn't roll
through when I did. G?
Them kids might
still be out there.
Or what if they came across
some other dude first.
some sick motherfucker in a van?
I'm a disaster. Marvin. I
don't know what else to say.
Where they mother at.
man? She need to take 'em.
'cause this shit here
ain't workin' for nobody.
Their mother is
around the corner
or around the world
or whistling around
the fuckin' graveyard
for all I know.
Haven't seen her in over a year.
And she's worse than me.
She turned me on to this shit.
and then she left me
when I tried to kick.
You ain't got no other family?
No one willing to help.
Burned all those
bridges a while ago.
Turns out. your family's
not too keen on helping you
when you steal from them.
You really are a
fuckin' mess. G.
I'm all too aware.
Engineering?
You know. work with machines?
Psychological operations?
What's that?
It's kind of like
communications.
You get trained to
deal with people
in unique situations.
Maybe.
Technology? You like science?
Sometimes.
There's also transportation.
Look... when y'all
came to my school.
you said you'd help
us pick a career
and train us and all that
so we could get good jobs later.
Sign me up for that.
That's why I came over
in the first place.
to show you what Juke
look like for your story.
But then I get here and find you
and your life all fucked up.
Man. fuck it. Give me that.
Shit don't matter no way.
Only thing that matters is.
is those little girls upstairs.
You need to clean
the fuck up. Gerald.
I wanna do better. Marvin.
But I don't know if I
can do it on my own.
You ain't doin' it
on your own. though.
I'm here.
♪ What's the 411? ♪
♪ I thought the
streets Was ill ♪
♪ Until I shot that gun ♪
♪ Wakin' up in cold sweats ♪
♪ I can't get no rest ♪
♪ I'm jumpin' out my sleep ♪
♪ I can barely
catch My breath ♪
♪ Havin' flashbacks When
I put them bullets... ♪
Ooh. I like this.
It's moving.
Emotionally. I mean.
♪ It got a homey stressed ♪
♪ I just tried to
get The dope... ♪
'Cause it's the damn truth.
♪ Now I'm left
With the regrets ♪
♪ I'm stuck with the effects ♪
- ♪ I'm livin' with a murder ♪
- Mm.
♪ Fuck. I really
Might confess ♪
♪ What if they got evidence? ♪
♪ What if they spoke
to residents? ♪
♪ It's messing with... ♪
Uh. my bad for bein' late.
I was caught up on some shit.
We gonna have a conversation
with these restaurant fools
'cause we need to
get this work movin'.
- But this shit with Lou...
- I know.
I damn near dropped my
phone when you told me.
Police is on ice for a minute.
but it won't stay
like that for long.
Scrap mama gonna
start talkin' louder.
How many other people you think
he speakin' with. Marvin. hmm?
If that nigga Howard
hadn't been there...
Look. your brother need
to make this shit right.
- Because if he don't...
- I get it. I'm on it.
A'ight.
Let's do this.
After whatever
happened to Unique.
my wife and I don't think
we want to do this anymore.
All that with 'Nique
ain't got nothin' to do
- with this work here.
- How do you know?
They still have not found him.
Because me and my sister
know what business look like.
And whatever happened to
'Nique wasn't business.
You gonna keep doin'
what you been doin'.
Ain't no backin' out now.
This makes us nervous.
This shit like Book
of the Month club.
You can't cancel your membership
just 'cause you don't
like readin' no more.
You signed on. Ain't
no signin' off.
And like Quân told y'all.
we your new partners now.
Ain't nothin' changed.
But this one spot.
it ain't enough.
We need to get bigger.
which is why we need to know
if y'all own any other shops.
We don't even own this one.
We just manage it.
My uncle owns the
Golden Pavilion
and 20 other restaurants
in Queens and Brooklyn.
Your uncle let you do
our work outta here?
He likes the extra income.
God bless America.
So where he at? And
how we gonna meet him?
You can meet him right
now. if you like.
That's him right there.
eating the number 37.
Yo. fuck outta here.
Number 37 my favorite too.
Must've ate somethin' bad.
Seem like you eat
somethin' bad a lot.
And what's that
supposed to mean?
Nothin'.
I'm workin' on it. Juke.
Good.
I kind of like we got
the black and green on.
It's... great minds think alike.
- It's my color.
- Kanan!
What's up. Iesha?
Hey. we. uh... you know.
we gotta get goin'.
The movie start in.
like. 30 minutes.
Ain't seen you around.
Guess you been busy with
them old-ass new friends
of yours from that party.
Y'all gonna ride down
to AC this weekend
and play them slots?
Those ain't my friends. Juke.
They just associates.
This nigga got associates now.
I mean. they all
seemed cool to me.
What was their names again?
- Snaps and...
- Pop. Snaps and Pop.
They used to stick up banks
until they started sellin' dope.
They teachin' you to be
a bank robber. Kanan?
They don't even do that
shit no more. Juke.
Yeah. I mean. they. like.
a hundred years old.
Hey. we gotta bounce.
- Come on.
- Later. Juke.
My cousin with Iesha...
You mean Pukebox?
You Jukebox. She Pukebox.
Stay the fuck away
from him. Krystal.
- Fuck you.
- Mm.
My business is like yours.
I find somethin' that works
and I repeat that shit.
Set it up in other spots
and get that market share.
I usually fuck with forks.
but I was tryin' to impress.
Market share means
nothing without profit.
Okay. word. Now. look at that.
That's what the fuck
I'm talkin' 'bout.
This work is all profit
for you and your family.
Ain't no cost to you.
We just usin' your space.
Space that you
payin' for already.
Variable incomes can be far
more lucrative than fixed.
I want a percentage
of your business.
We will share in
success and failure.
That's a conversation I might
be willing to have with you.
After you show me them
locations you talkin' 'bout.
Oh.
Every restaurant I own.
Do they have the number
37 at all those spots?
Not always the
number 37. but yes.
That's what the fuck
I'm talkin' 'bout.
We gonna check these out.
and then we'll
circle back on you.
What for?
Would you just wait
for me. please?
It's too fast. Kanan.
It's my bad.
I-I just...
I just really like you a lot.
that's all.
And I like you too.
You like me too?
Mm.
All right. I'm goin' home.
What? No. no. no.
Iesha. l-l-look. look. I
won't do it again. a'ight?
It's my fault.
Nah. I need to go home.
Well. fuck it. then.
A'ight. whatever. Go.
So you not gonna take me home?
I'ma sit and watch the
rest of this movie.
You know how to take a train.
That's real messed up. Kanan.
Whatever.
You done lost your fucking
mind this time. Lou.
No. My mind right where
I left it at. big bro.
Yo... y-yo. Yo! Yo!
You wanna kill yourself?
Do it. nigga.
But you ain't takin'
the rest of us with you.
Yo. fuck that
mean. man? Ease up.
I ain't even do nothin'.
You almost... you on
some more Raq bullshit.
Nah. this your bullshit.
You the one went
to Scrap's moms.
Fuck you talkin' 'bout?
Your drunk ass stumbled
into Scrap's moms' crib and
told her what went down.
Fuck you.
Nah. you done fucked
us first. nigga.
She went to the police. Lou.
She dropped your fuckin'
name. sayin' you told her
what happened.
If she went to the police.
how come I ain't
down there right now?
Raq got her mans inside.
Well. I-I don't remember...
even goin' there.
Well. you did.
And you got real chatty. nigga.
Now you gotta clean
all this shit up.
I want you to feel good.
And I want you to
make me feel good.
Why you here?
Because I live here. Ronnie.
You stayin' with your mother.
I'm just gettin' some
things for Jerome.
Why-why is the lady
from the bodega here?
Get your shit and go.
This is still
'Nique's and my house.
Get your shit...
and go.
It's not good for people
to see us together.
Pernessa ain't nothin'
to worry about.
She doesn't like you.
I don't give a fuck.
You should.
Enemies are dangerous.
especially when they're family.
Captain Burke.
Detective Howard.
How you holdin' up. sir?
Every day's the same.
And then every night...
I remember some
new fuckin' regret.
Some memory of something I
fucked up with my daughter
that I can't fix.
I hear you.
Everything there?
Far as I can tell.
Hey. listen. if I
can ever do anything.
just let me know.
I will.
I got some paperwork to get to.
Yeah. Go do your job.
I'm fine. Thank you.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- How are you?
- Good. How can I help you?
Just wonderin'
what kind of things
y'all supply restaurants with.
Uh. equipment.
cookware. tableware.
janitorial supplies.
and... other stuff.
Who are you?
I'm sorry.
Uh. my name is Raquel Thomas.
and I might be gettin' into
the restaurant business myself.
so I was just doin'
a little research.
You the owner?
My brother and I
own this company.
but we only supply
Chinese restaurants.
We cannot help you.
So I don't look like I
could own a Chinese spot?
We're very busy.
Well. I'll let you get
back to work. then.
Thanks for your time.
Y'all have a good day.
Hey. what's up. Cap?
You wanted to see me?
I hope you don't think
it's okay to show up late
over at. uh. Queens Narcotics.
I got it?
You're on the one-yard line.
All you need to do
now is walk it in.
Congratulations. unofficially.
Unofficially.
So that means there's still
a hoop I gotta get through.
Relax. The paperwork's in.
As far as the department's
concerned. it's done.
These feds and this task force
gotta run an enhanced
background check.
talk to a few
folks who know you.
It's a formality.
Makes 'em feel important.
Unless you're a serial
killer. you should be fine.
As long as they don't talk
to any of Howard's
old girlfriends.
he'll be okay.
Who you lookin' for?
The fuck outta my way. man.
He asked you who
you lookin' for.
And I ain't fuckin'
talkin' to you.
Get the fuck off me!
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Kanan cousin.
Punk-ass mu'fuckers.
Next time. call first. let
me know you comin' through.
Why the fuck would I do that?
Hey. how the group?
Y'all choose a lead?
What are you doin'. Kanan?
Fuck you mean. what am I doin'?
I'm doin' what I do.
I'm livin' this life.
Talk to this fool
and the rest of these
niggas that way.
but don't talk that shit to me.
I wiped the snot out
your nose. nigga.
I know who the fuck you are.
What you want?
Iesha told me about the movie.
Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Oh. it's like that?
I told you to be right with her.
I told you if you
fuck that shit up.
you'll fuck up this
music I'm doin'.
Aw. Butta's a'ight. Juke.
And so is Iesha.
She's just too damn young.
Probably more your type.
I got shit to do.
None of this shit
you doin' with him
make you grown. Kanan.
You still a
scared-ass little boy
tryin' to show
his mama he a man.
I can talk to her.
You ain't never talkin' to her.
My family ain't got nothin'
to do with you and me.
There she is.
I appreciate you
meetin' me. Adina.
I was just down at the precinct
gathering Shannon's things...
when I saw this.
I thought you might
want to have it.
I'm sorry for how
I acted toward you.
And I'm sorry for how
I acted toward Shannon.
But it's too late
to make that right.
Look. I know I'll never get
an answer that'll satisfy me.
And I'll never truly understand
why my daughter
did what she did.
But I need to at least try.
Is there anything I should know?
Anything she did or said?
You're asking me if I know
why Shannon killed herself?
My guess is. it was everything.
It was me. It was you.
It was the job.
When that girl from the
Upper East Side overdosed
and Shannon got
dragged into it...
it fucked her up.
All of a sudden.
IAD's openin' an
investigation into her?
It was unfair and wrong.
She was obsessed with Howard.
convinced he was hiding things.
And I'll tell you the
same thing I told her.
I'm not goin' anywhere
near Howard and all that.
That's got nothin'
to do with me.
And that's all I gotta
say. Captain Burke.
We both lost a lot
when Shannon died.
I'm sorry for us.
Me too.
This where your moms live?
Are you followin' me. Ronnie?
We family.
Whoever did all that at the
tailor shop still out here.
You gotta be careful. Pernessa.
I got shit to do. Ronnie.
Don't want nothin'
to happen to you.
You all Jerome got left.
I gotta go.
Hi. Lou-Lou.
As usual. your timing's
fuckin' perfect.
Little early for
all that. isn't it?
And it's a little too late
for you to give a fuck.
What you want. Ma?
I need cash.
Your sister's short.
and I got bills to pay.
That's what I got.
Your brother tells me you
part owner of this club.
and this is all you got
to give your mother?
You know. your daddy
spent way too much time
in joints just like this.
And you saw what it did to him.
This ain't what did it to him.
You take care of
yourself. Lou-Lou.
You too.
Your mother.
That's what it says
on the paperwork.
So he messin' with
'Nique's brother
but you don't know
what the work is?
He also kickin' it
with some old heads.
Bonnie and Clyde and all them.
Kanan fuckin' with
Snaps and Pop?
And... Famous moved out.
When? Why?
I don't know.
But Kanan's changin'. Aunt Raq.
He ain't the same.
Kind of bold.
you callin' me up like you did.
You don't like bold girls?
Nah. I like 'em just fine.
Then you 'bout to
like me a whole lot.
Don't remember
bein' here before.
And I definitely don't
remember sayin' all that shit.
And that's why
right there. nigga.
That shit fuckin'
up your whole life.
This is just a symptom
of somethin' else.
Just like Scrap mom.
No. This shit all on you. Lou.
If Scrap moms the symptom.
you're the fuckin'
disease. nigga.
I don't want this.
But...
I'm sorry.
Just fuckin' sorry.
That's that.
Never believed in ghosts.
That's just shit
people tell they kids
to scare 'em and keep
'em in bed at night.
But memories just like ghosts.
They all the bad you done
and seen and felt and known.
And the thing is.
the more you try to
push that shit back
and wipe it out your brain.
the stronger it gets.
It ain't got nowhere to go.
and it wants you
to know it's there.
So when you at your weakest.
that's when it reminds you...
of your worst shit.
of your worst day.
of your worst you.
♪ I wish somebody. yeah ♪
♪ Would come and ease my ♪
♪ Troublin' mind ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I wish somebody ♪
♪ Would come and ease my ♪
♪ Troublin' mind ♪
♪ Oh. yes. I do ♪
♪ Why won't somebody. yeah ♪
♪ Come and ease my ♪
♪ Troublin' mind ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I sure wish somebody ♪
♪ Would come and ease my ♪
♪ Troublin' mind ♪
♪ Oh. yes. I do ♪
♪ I wish my baby. yeah ♪
♪ Would come and tell me ♪
♪ Everything's all right ♪